adidasyeezy-350.us.com 2018-09-27

# Privacy Notice : Yeezy Boost 350

##  Privacy Notice

At our shop, we believe that understanding what our customers want for products, services and information is an essential part to build an interesting and useful online environment. We've done our business with this belief in mind. We've created this privacy police so that you have easy access to information about our privacy practices. Please note that this policy applies only to information collected by our shop and does not extend to any other website.

The Information We Collects and Uses

We do not automatically log personal data, nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. Cookies are placed / collected to monitor visits but not used to store personal data. We will collect and store information about you to allow us to firstly, process and fulfill any order requirements (e.g., name, address, telephone number(s), credit card information, email address, etc.) and secondly to provide you with the best possible service. You may also enter your birth date when you registered, that if you purchase from our website at your birthday, we will happy to give you a surprise.

our shop does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of thirteen. If you are under thirteen, please ask your patents to register and/or use the online store.

**Sharing of Personal Information**

our shop will neither disclose nor sell any information about you unless required to do so by law or in connection with a legal claim or proceeding.  
our shop may appoint third party service providers to administer and/or operate certain functions or services on our behalf, the proper performance of which may require a transfer of the information submitted by you. The functions or services include, for example, administering this site, delivery of products requested or ordered by you, and delivery of marketing or other communications to you about our products, services or special events. Any such transfer shall be subject to confidentiality and security obligations and for the sole purpose of the performance of those functions or services.

**Security**

We store your personal information on a secure server and use procedures designed to protect the personal information we collect from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. Although we will take (and require our third-party providers to take) commercially reasonable security precautions regarding your personal information collected and stored on the site, due to the open nature of the Internet, we cannot guarantee that any of your personal information stored in our servers, or transmitted to or from a user, will be free from unauthorized access, and we disclaim any liability for any theft or loss of, unauthorized access or damage to, or interception of any data or communications. By using the Site, you acknowledge that you understand and agree to assume these risks.

**About Cookies**

Cookies are pieces of information a web site can send to your computer's browser for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to ascertain which web pages are visited and how often, to make our web site more user friendly, and to give you a better experience when you return to the website. For example, cookies allow us to save your password so you do not have to re-enter it every time you visit our site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you do not have to accept them. To disable cookies, you should access the help tab on your browser or read the information that came with your browser software. However, your visit to our website will be significantly enhanced if cookies are not disabled. If you do not disable your cookies, you accept our collection and storage of any of your personal information such cookies contain.

We may from time to time modify privacy policy and will post a copy of the amended policy at our shop. If you do not agree to, or cannot comply with this policy, you should not use the site. You will be deemed to have accepted the amended policy if you continue to use the site after any amendments is posted on the site.
